Your heart is God’s room, not sitting room.
“Your heart is God’s room” means “Your heart is prayer room”, not sitting room.
“Your heart is God’s room” means “God’s prayer room”.
What are you doing with your heart?
Have you forgiven those who have sinned against you?
What are you holding?
Is your heart imprisoned – pain of the past, envy and jealousy?
If your heart is not free, there is no place for God because your heart is God's room.
You have the opportunity, grace now before we begin to pray.
You can begin to reconcile now.
Say to yourself, “I mean it”.
Whether you are right or wrong – someone wronged you – you have no right to hold offence.
If you hold a grudge against your brother, you have already grieved the Holy Spirit.
A grudge against a brother - whether you are right...
You were intentionally cheated for a reason not known to you...
Viewers all over the world, we cannot pray without the Holy Ghost.
You must know where you belong before we pray.
Where do I belong?
I know where I belong.
I belong to the presence of God because in His presence, you are strong, content, satisfied.
Overflow Congregation
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Right now, begin to reconcile yourself.
Begin to forgive and forget.
Forgive me as I forgive those who sin against me.
In Jesus Christ’s name, we pray.
(Amen.)
You must mean it.
You must allow your heart to speak for you because the real thing about you is your heart.
Your spirit, your heart is the real thing.
Allow your heart to speak for you.
Mean it with all your heart.
In Jesus’ name, we pray.
(Amen.)
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Those of us that are still wrestling with our past, pain of the past, offence in the past,
I pray you will be released, in the name of Jesus.
(Amen!)
Be released, in the name of Jesus.
You are not here to meet a man but you are here to meet God.
God is not a man.
In Jesus’ name, you are released.
(Amen.)
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
(Amen!)
From the pain of the past, be released in the name of Jesus.
From that bitterness, be released, in the name of Jesus.
(Amen!)
Be released, in the name of Jesus.
Viewers, I lay my hand upon you, to release you from that pain of the past.
(Amen!)
I lay my hand upon you.
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
(Amen!)
Pain of the past, be released, in the name of Jesus!
Receive that nature of God, in the name of Jesus.
(Amen!)
In Jesus Christ's name.
Amen.
(Amen.)
I want to believe you are released.
Will you believe with me?
You can be seated.
Since you believe with me - two believers are better than one, if they are one.
Since you believe with me that you are released, you are released.
(Amen.)
Now, you can sense God’s presence.
Are you sensing God’s presence?
(Yes.)
It is your time to meet the Lord.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Hallelujah.
As we move, the Spirit releases His message.
These are faith words that will build you, not just counsel.
Hallelujah.
(Amen.)
When we say, “I am a faith man”, many of us don’t know what it means.
We just hear people saying, "I'm a faith man; I'm a faith woman."
What does it mean to you to say, “I’m a faith man; I’m a faith woman”?
That is our name as Christians - "I'm a man of faith."
You shouldn't call yourself a "faith woman" when you don't know what it means.
It means I trust in God with all my faith.
I'm a "faith woman"... - women, can somebody talk here?
To believe the Word of God...
When we say, “I am a faith man”, it means you use faith words and produce faith results.
That is it.
You use faith words.
Do you know what it means to use faith words?
If I say I am a faith man, I am using faith words to produce faith results.
If it does not produce faith results, it means my faith is faith in faith,
not faith in the finished works of our Lord Jesus Christ.
What do I mean by the language of the Bible?
That is the language God used to create and to save us, to heal, to bless, to judge and to rule over us.
That is the language of the Bible.
The language of today is the language we use every time out there, to gossip, give instruction,
"Do this! You can do this!" - you don't mind what you say;
to talk to your children, "Please, you are stupid. Come here",
to sing songs - anybody can sing songs, even gospel songs, not even being a Christian,
to tell stories - this is the language of today,
to do business - you have a lot of fake business cards - stories, telling lies,
to do politics of today.
That is the language of today.
When you now say, “I’m a faith man” or “I’m a faith woman”,
it means you use faith words and produce faith results.